

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Mobile App Development Web Development Game Development Ruby programming language C++ programming language Node JS

## PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit Reliable and professional Organized Time management Team player Fast learner Motivated

#### INTERESTS

Photography Music (EDM/Instrumental) Cinema Travelling **Exploring Cuisines** Linux command Line

## CONTACT

P: +91 9880808152/ +91 7619488873 E: jaseemabdul20@gmail.com W:www.jaseemabdul12.wixsite.com/ mysite

# ABDUL JASEEM CK

# APP DEVELOPER

# **ABOUT**

I'm an Android Developer, passionate about building great apps. For me app development is not just about coding, it's also about creating an awesome user experience. I'm also an enthusiastic learner when it comes to new programming languages and exploring different areas including and not limited to web development.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### APP DEVELOPER

App.Labs | Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

- Developed a Social Media App much like popular platforms such as Instagram with the use of Firebase Cloud Functionality, from scratch.
- Implemented a comfortable User Experience

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Suphalaam Technologies | Jan 2020 - April 2020

- Developed webpages as per company requirements
- Improved on the existing applications and released them on Google Play store
- Added new features and fixing bugs.

# SENIOR APP DEVELOPER

Tarezameen Foundation | Jul 2020 - Present

• Developing an App for the organization as per requirements

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION (GAME AND MOBILE APP **DEVELOPMENT** 

CMR University, 2017-2020

## **TOOLS**

- VS Code
- Android Studio
- XCode
- Unity
- Unreal Engine
- Git
- Slack
- Trello Figma
- Photoshop
- Cocos2dx